{
  "GK": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "The World Largest desert is ?",
      "option_1": "Thar",
      "option_2": "Kalahari",
      "option_3": "Sahara",
      "option_4": "Sonoran",
      "correct_option": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "The gas used for making vegetables is ?",
      "option_1": "Oxygen",
      "option_2": "Carbon dioxide",
      "option_3": "Hydrogen",
      "option_4": "Nitrogen",
      "correct_option": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "In 200 2 crossed the heliosheath boundary and into the vast region at the edge of our solar system where the solar wind runs up against the thin gas between the stars. What did this crossing confirm about the shape of our solar system?",
      "option_1": "It’s round",
      "option_2": "It’s squashed",
      "option_3": "It’s like a donut",
      "option_4": "It’s a horseshoe shape",
      "correct_option": 2
    }
  ],
  
  "Sports": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Which is the only Grand Slam tournament to use Clay Court?",
      "option_1": "US Open",
      "option_2": "French Open",
      "option_3": "Australia Open",
      "option_4": "Wimbledon",
      "correct_option": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Three R’s of Football are famous in which country ?",
      "option_1": "Brazil",
      "option_2": "USA",
      "option_3": "Argentina",
      "option_4": "India",
      "correct_option": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Which Commonwealth Games were hosted in India?",
      "option_1": "2002",
      "option_2": "2006",
      "option_3": "1998",
      "option_4": "2010",
      "correct_option": 4
    },
      {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Holkar Trophy is associated with which sport?",
      "option_1": "Bridge",
      "option_2": "Hocket",
      "option_3": "Football",
      "option_4": "Badminton",
      "correct_option": 1
    },
      {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "What is the name of person which controls a football match",
      "option_1": "Umpire",
      "option_2": "Referee",
      "option_3": "Spectator",
      "option_4": "Goalkeeper",
      "correct_option": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "The National Game of Japan is...",
      "option_1": "Tennis",
      "option_2": "Ice Hockey",
      "option_3": "Sumo Wrestling",
      "option_4": "Karate",
      "correct_option": 3
    },
     {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Where did MS Dhoni make his ODI debut ?",
      "option_1": "Dhaka",
      "option_2": "Chiitagong",
      "option_3": "Hyderabad",
      "option_4": "Vishakhapatnam",
      "correct_option": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Who is the only cricketer to score two successive centuries in a world cup?",
      "option_1": "Rahul Dravid",
      "option_2": "Sachin Tendulkar",
      "option_3": "Saurav Ganguly",
      "option_4": "Virender Sehwag",
      "correct_option": 1
    },
     {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Boat race is a famous festival game of which state?",
      "option_1": "Assam",
      "option_2": "Goa",
      "option_3": "Tamil Nadu",
      "option_4": "Kerala",
      "correct_option": 4
    },
     {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "In archery, what shape is the target?",
      "option_1": "Square",
      "option_2": "Triangular",
      "option_3": "Round",
      "option_4": "Rectangular",
      "correct_option": 3
    }
    ]
  
}
